

Michael Myziura CV

Senior JavaScript Front-end Developer (Vue.js | Nuxt.js)

LinkedIn | Github | Email | Code examples



Skills

Front-End

- JavaScript (ES6+) 5 years
- HTML5 / CSS3 (SCSS) 5 years
- Vue 2 / Nuxt 2 / Vuex / Webpack 5 years
- Vue 3 (Composition API) / Nuxt 3 / Pinia / Vite < 1 year
- PWA, Tailwind CSS, Element UI, Bootstrap, Vuetify, Pixel Perfect, etc

Back-End

- Node.js / Express 2 years
- MongoDB / Mongoose 2 years

Other

- · REST API architecture
- · CI/CD with Heroku, VPS
- Testing (unit, E2E, smoke)
- Babel, ESLint, Prettier, Iodash, i18n, dayjs, socket.io, code review

Languages

- English professional working proficiency
- Ukrainian native proficiency



Work Experience

- Kernel October 2019 present
 - Transithub*
- Freelance 2016 October 2019
 - Zlott
 - Homefair
 - Wexplors*
 - ICO Forum
 - ICO CustomCoin Platform, etc
- Own projects in free time
 - Captions Clash*
- * described below in «Projects» section



Transithub October 2019 - March 2022

The customer is the largest producer of sunflower oil in Ukraine, as well as one of the leading suppliers of agro-industrial products on the international market. Transithub is a large logistics project. It has been developing for more than 4 years and is already working. The main goal is to create a platform for connecting drivers who need to deliver some goods by trucks with dispatchers at factories, warehouses and seaports.

Responsibilities:

- · Implementing the most complex tasks, front-end architecture
- · Implementing new technologies to improve the code
- · Maintaining existing functionality
- · Code review and refactoring
- · Participation in front-end performance analysis and estimation tasks
- · Daily meetings with the team and the product owner's representative
- Tracking the updates for existing technologies and implementing new ones

Technologies: JavaScript (ES6+), Vue 2, Nuxt 2, Vuex, Webpack, HTML5 / CSS3 (SCSS), Tailwind CSS, i18n, dayjs, axios, lodash, prettier, eslint, npm, yarn, REST API, etc

Role: Senior JavaScript Front-end Developer (Vue.js | Nuxt.js)

Team: 7 members

Wexplors 2018 - 2019

It is an aggregator website for finding plane tickets. We compare all available flight options at your request from popular Kiwi and Aviasales sources, and then we direct clients to the official websites of airlines and agencies for purchase. Thanks to the many options and filters, the client can find the right ticket for himself.

Responsibilities:

- · Implementing the most complex tasks, front-end architecture
- · Implementing new technologies to improve the code
- · Creating from scratch and deployment
- Project management
- Code review
- · Performance analysis & SEO
- · Hebrew support, including right-to-left layouts
- · Participation in front-end performance analysis and estimation tasks

Technologies: JavaScript (ES6 6+), Vue 2, HTML5 / CSS3 (SCSS), Vuex, Socket.io, Heroku, Webpack, Babel, i18n, momentjs, axios, lodash, eslint, npm, REST API, etc

Role: JavaScript Front-end Developer & Product Manager

Team: 4 members

Captions Clash in free time

An online multiplayer game for a group of friends, in which you have to come up with a context around funny gifs, compete with friends, vote for the best options, have a lot of fun and, of course, win. Similar to The Jackbox Party or Uno games.

Responsibilities:

- Full-stack development
- Deployment

- · Performance tuning
- End-To-End testing multiple users with Selenium & Mocha

Technologies: JavaScript (ES6+), Vue 2, Vuex, HTML5 / CSS3 (SCSS), Tailwind CSS, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Socket.io, Webpack, Tailwind CSS, Heroku, axios, Iodash, prettier, eslint, REST API, etc

Role: Full-Stack JavaScript Developer Vue.js & Node.js

Team: 1 member



Education

Poltava National Technological University

• Bachelor's degree of Computer Science 2017 - 2021



About

I am an ambitious and motivated front-end developer with vast experience in creating complex and interesting projects.

I am a fast learner. I always put a great accent on the accuracy and quality of my work. I pursue ambitious career goals and offer my view on solving problems and performing tasks during the discussions.



Research interests

- TypeScript
- Sentry
- VueUse
- · Real-time projects with Socket.io